<doc sitename="EIKE - Europäisches Institut für Klima &amp; Energie" title="Program – 13th International Conference on Climate and Energy" author="Michael Poost" source="https://eike-klima-energie.eu/13thconference/program/" hostname="eike-klima-energie.eu" excerpt="22 - 23 November 2019, NH München East Conference Center, Münich, Germany All talks and Q&amp;A are interpreted simultaneously: English-German and German-English" categories="" tags="" fingerprint="CyFEzcexicDZKb41VMIlQ+r5VpQ=">
  <main>
    <head rend="h3">22 – 23 November 2019, NH München East Conference Center, Münich, Germany</head>
    <head rend="h4">All talks and Q&amp;A are interpreted simultaneously: English-German and German-English</head>
    <table>
      <row>
        <cell>10.00 Hrs</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>10.15 Hrs</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>17.45 Hrs</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>11.15 Hrs</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>12.15 Hrs – 13.45 Hrs</cell>
        <cell>Break – Joint Lunch at the Conference Centre</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>13.45 Hrs</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>14.15 Hrs</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>15.30 Hrs</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>16.15 Hrs – 16.45 Hrs</cell>
        <cell>Break</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>16.45 Hrs</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>17.45 Hrs</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>18.45 Hrs</cell>
        <cell>Joint Dinner</cell>
      </row>
    </table>
    <p>Friday, 22 November</p>
    <p>Welcome and Introduction<lb/>Defending Science<lb/>Dr. Holger Thuß<lb/>President, Europäisches Institut für Klima und Energie (EIKE)</p>
    <p>Welcome<lb/>Dealing with Climate Alarmism in the United States<lb/>James Taylor<lb/>Senior fellow for environment and energy policy at The Heartland Institute</p>
    <p>EU Klimapolitik und der Brexit<lb/>Dr. Benny Peiser<lb/>Director, Global Warming Policy Foundation</p>
    <p>Technically almost everything is possible…<lb/>Energy-Transformation between Dream and Reality<lb/>Prof. Dr. Helmut Alt<lb/>University of Applied Sciences, Aachen</p>
    <p>The Real Condition of the Great Barrier Reef<lb/>Prof. Dr. Peter Ridd – via Skype<lb/>Former head of the Marine Geophysical Laboratory, James Cook University, Australia</p>
    <p>The Influence of Green House Gases on Climate: Research in the Field and in the Laboratory<lb/>Dr. Michael Schnell<lb/>Universität Rostock, Zentralinstitut für organische Chemie Berlin-Adlershof Feinchemie Schwebda GmbH</p>
    <p>Detection of UHI bias in China climate network using Tmin and Tmax surface temperature divergence<lb/>Prof. Dr. Nicola Scafetta<lb/>Università di Napoli Federico II, Dipartimento di Scienze della Terra</p>
    <p>The Polar Bear Catastrophe that never happened<lb/>Dr. Susan Crockford<lb/>Scientist and author</p>
    <p>US Climate Policy 3 years after the Presidential Election – Talk and Discussion via Skype<lb/>Myron Ebell<lb/>Head of President-elect Trump’s Transition Team to reform the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) and quitting the Paris-Agreement, Director of Energy &amp; Environmental Policy, Competitive Enterprise Institute</p>
    <table>
      <row>
        <cell>9.00 Hrs</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>10.00 Hrs</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>10.45 Hrs – 11.15 Hrs</cell>
        <cell>Break</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>11.15 Hrs</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>13.00 Hrs – 14.30 Hrs</cell>
        <cell>Break – Joint Lunch at the Conference Center</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>14.30 Hrs</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>15.00 Hrs</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>15.45 Hrs</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>16.15 Hrs – 16.45 Hrs</cell>
        <cell>Break</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>16.45 Hrs</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>17.30 Hrs</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>18.15 Hrs</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>18.45 Hrs</cell>
      </row>
      <row>
        <cell>Followed by (18:50 h) Reception</cell>
      </row>
    </table>
    <p>Saturday, 23 November</p>
    <p>Climate Change and the melting Alpine Glaciers<lb/>Prof. em. Dr. Christian Schlüchter<lb/>University of Bern, Institute for Geologie</p>
    <p>About the Reliability of Climate Models<lb/>Prof. Dr. Nicola Scafetta<lb/>Università di Napoli Federico II, Dipartimento di Scienze della Terra</p>
    <p>Which Role did the Sun Play in Climate Change? What does it mean for us?<lb/>Prof. Dr. Henrik Svensmark<lb/>Centre for Sun-Climate Research des Danish National Space Centre</p>
    <p>Prof. Dr. Nir Shaviv<lb/>Racah Institute of Physics – The Hebrew University of Jerusalem</p>
    <p>What you always wanted to know about Climate Change…<lb/>Dipl.-Ing. Michael Limburg<lb/>Vice-President, Europäisches Institut für Klima und Energie (EIKE)</p>
    <p>How much of the Climate is man-made<lb/>Dr. Sebastian Lüning<lb/>Die kalte Sonne</p>
    <p>Natural Limitations of the German Energy Transition<lb/>Prof. Dr. Horst Lüdecke<lb/>Press Spokes Person, Europäisches Institut für Klima und Energie (EIKE)</p>
    <p>Climate Panic – Radiation Panic<lb/>Dr. Lutz Niemann<lb/>Physicist and former Radiation Protection Officer</p>
    <p>Nuclear Power of the 21st Century<lb/>Dr. rer. nat. Götz Ruprecht<lb/>Institute for Solid State-Nuclear Physics gGmbH</p>
    <p>Saving the Climate by Abolishing Democracy?<lb/>Günter Ederer<lb/>Author, Film Producer and Economic Editor</p>
    <p>Closing Remarks<lb/>Wolfgang Müller<lb/>Generals Secretary, Europäisches Institut für Klima und Energie (EIKE)</p>
    <p>All talks and Q&amp;A are interpreted simultaneously: English-German and German-English</p>
    <p>Registration: Please register online on the EIKE website or send your registration to EIKE via:<lb/>Email: info@eike.pw, Fax: +49-3641-3279-8589, Mail: Wiesenstr. 110 2, 07743 Jena, Germany</p>
    <p>The EIKE is funded exclusively by private contributions. Donations in Germany are tax deductible.</p>
  </main>
  <comments>
    <head>Neueste Kommentare</head>
  </comments>
</doc>