<doc sitename="EIKE - Europäisches Institut für Klima &amp; Energie" title="Imprint" author="Michael Poost" source="https://eike-klima-energie.eu/imprint/" hostname="eike-klima-energie.eu" excerpt="Site Notice Information pursuant to Sect. 5 German Telemedia Act (TMG) EIKE e.V Wiesenstr. 110 07743 Jena Represented by: Dr. Holger Thuß, Präsident" categories="" tags="" fingerprint="vRIx7O8TAf8dvKwQVg3xa6BZNPI=">
  <main>
    <head rend="h1">Site Notice</head>
    <head rend="h2">Information pursuant to Sect. 5 German Telemedia Act (TMG)</head>
    <p>EIKE e.V<lb/>Wiesenstr. 110<lb/>07743 Jena</p>
    <p>Represented by:<lb/>Dr. Holger Thuß, Präsident<lb/>Dipl. Ing. Michael Limburg, Vizepäsident (Medien &amp; Politik)<lb/>Prof. Dr. Horst-Joachim Lüdecke (Dipl.-Physiker), Pressesprecher<lb/>Dipl. Meteorologe Klaus-Eckart Puls, Pressesprecher</p>
    <head rend="h2">Contact</head>
    <p>Phone: +49 (0)3641-3279 8581<lb/>E-mail: info(at)eike-klima-energie.eu</p>
    <head rend="h2">Person responsible for editorial</head>
    <p>Dipl. Ing. Michael Limburg, Vizepäsident (Medien &amp; Politik)</p>
    <head rend="h2">EU dispute resolution</head>
    <p>The European Commission provides a platform for online dispute resolution (ODR): https://ec.europa.eu/consumers/odr/.<lb/>Our e-mail address can be found above in the site notice.</p>
    <head rend="h2">Dispute resolution proceedings in front of a consumer arbitration board</head>
    <p>We are not willing or obliged to participate in dispute resolution proceedings in front of a consumer arbitration board.</p>
    <head rend="h3">Donation Account:</head>
    <p>Account owner: EIKE e.V.<lb/>Bank: Volksbank Gera Jena Rudolstadt<lb/>IBAN: DE34 8309 4454 0042 4292 01<lb/>BIC/SWIFT: GENODEF1RUJ</p>
    <head rend="h3">Non-profit organization</head>
    <p>The responsible tax authority office has certified our institute that it serves solely and directly charitable purposes, similar to American 501(c) organizations.</p>
    <head rend="h3">Disclaimer</head>
    <p>In the individual case of marked articles and pictures, all rights are reserved. All texts, pictures, graphics, sound, video and animation files, as well as their arrangements, are subject to copyright and other laws for the protection of intellectual property. They may neither be copied, modified or used on other websites for commercial purposes or for distribution purposes. Some pages contain information that is subject to the copyright of those who have provided it. Articles, publications, or contributions of a different kind, which are specifically marked, express exclusively the opinion of the author or authors. The editorial team of EIKE is not responsible for this.</p>
    <head rend="h3">Guarantee / Liability</head>
    <p>The information on this website is provided without any warranty or guarantee of any kind, may they be expressed or implied. Even if it is assumed that the information given here is correct, they may still contain mistakes or inaccuracies. Therefore, no liability is assumed for incorrect, imprecise or incomplete information on these web pages or for possible consequences resulting from the use of the information.</p>
    <p>© by EIKE | imprint</p>
  </main>
  <comments>
    <head>Neueste Kommentare</head>
  </comments>
</doc>