<doc sitename="EIKE - Europäisches Institut für Klima &amp; Energie" title="1. Geoethik Konferenz über Klimawandel – Wissenschaft und Geoethik am 8 &amp; 9.9.16 in London" author="Webadmin" date="2016-07-29" source="https://eike-klima-energie.eu/2016/07/29/1-geoethik-konferenz-ueber-klimawandel-wissenschaft-und-geoethik-am-8-9-9-16-in-london/" hostname="eike-klima-energie.eu" excerpt="Das Independent Committee in Geoethics (1) führt am 8 &amp; 9.9.16 in London seine erste wissenschaftliche Konferenz zum Thema „Climate Change - Science und Geoethics“ durch. Teilnehmen können alle, die an der wissenschaftlichen Wahrheit über den Klimawandel interessiert sind. Hervorragende Wissenschaftler aus aller Welt haben bereits ihre Teilnahme zugesagt. Konferenzsprache ist Englisch. Der Eintritt ist kostenlos, Spenden jedoch sehr erwünscht. Ort: Main Hall der Conway Hall am Red Lion Square (Holborn).Conway Hall liegt im Zentrum von London udn ist per U-Bahn leicht zu erreichen. Diese Information wird für eine Weile oben &quot;kleben&quot;." categories="Klima" tags="" fingerprint="7596IzHxQUfmPGoK8EGcM9//Rvs=">
  <main>
    <head rend="h1">Programm</head>
    <head rend="h2">Registration</head>
    <p>Anyone wanting to participate is very welcome – there is plenty of space.</p>
    <p>Register by informing: Nils-Axel Mörner – morner@pog.nu</p>
    <p>No registration fee – but voluntary donations are appreciated.</p>
    <head rend="h2">Accommodation</head>
    <p>At your own organization or via advice from our event-co-ordinator:</p>
    <p>Ross March – R.marsh_al_sabti@hotmail.co.uk</p>
    <head rend="h2">Extended Abstracts &amp; Commentary Notes</head>
    <p>This Conference Volume will be posted on ResearchGate well in time before the event.</p>
    <head rend="h2">Programme</head>
    <p>(may be somewhat adjusted) Thursday 8 September: Natural drivers of climate changes</p>
    <p>08.30 Registration (uploading of ppt-files)</p>
    <p>08.50 Welcome</p>
    <p>Session 1: Planet Earth in the cosmos</p>
    <p>09.00 Athem Alsabti: Effects of Nearby Supernovae on Atmosphere and Climate</p>
    <p>09.20 Oliver Manuel: Neutron Repulsion *</p>
    <p>09.30 Discussion</p>
    <p>09.40 Tea and coffee</p>
    <p>Session 2: Influence of the Sun and the major planets on the Earth’s climate</p>
    <p>10.00 Nils-Axel Mörner: An introduction to planetary-solar-terrestrial interaction</p>
    <p>10.10 Roger Tattersall &amp; Richard Salvador: Does solar system orbital motion and resonance synchronize solar variation, LOD and ENSO?</p>
    <p>10.20 Ned Nikolov &amp; Karl Zeller: A new planetary temperature model and its implication for the Greenhouse theory</p>
    <p>10.40 Nicola Scafetta: Multi-frequency spectral coherence between planetary and global surface temperature oscillations</p>
    <p>11.00 Jan-Erik Solheim: Ice margins, the Sun and the planets</p>
    <p>11.20 Per Strandberg: Drivers of ENSO variability</p>
    <p>11.40 Discussion</p>
    <p>12:00–13.00: Lunch (at your own)</p>
    <p>Session 3: Ocean variability</p>
    <p>13.00 Fred Goldberg: Are the ocean currents affecting our climate?</p>
    <p>13.10 Martin Hovland: Documented pH and temperature anomalies in the deep ocean *</p>
    <p>13.30 Wyss Yim: Sub-aerial and submarine volcanic eruptions and climatic variability</p>
    <p>13.50 Discussion</p>
    <p>Session 4: Natural influences on climate</p>
    <p>15.00 Peter Ward: Ozone depletion, not greenhouse warming, caused recent warming *</p>
    <p>15.20 Hans Jelbring: The dominant physical processes that cause climate change</p>
    <p>15.40 Alex Pope: Ice on land</p>
    <p>16.00 Tea and coffee</p>
    <p>16.20 Fabio Pistella and Leonello Serva: The CHIC project of ICG</p>
    <p>16.50 Discussion</p>
    <p>17.00 Close</p>
    <p>* Keynote presentations</p>
    <p>Friday 9 September: The temperature plot and its consequences</p>
    <p>08.30 mingle and uploading of ppt-files</p>
    <p>08.50 Welcome</p>
    <p>Session 5: The greenhouse effect and anthropogenic global warming</p>
    <p>09.00 Jan-Erik Solheim: Result of a greenhouse experiment</p>
    <p>09.20 Francois Gervais: Tiny CO2 warming challenged by Earth greening</p>
    <p>09.40 Fred Goldberg: Does human CO2 emission change the climate? Faith vs. facts</p>
    <p>10.00 Tea and coffee</p>
    <p>10.20 Albrecht Glatzle: Reconsidering livestock’s role in climate change *</p>
    <p>10.40 Pamela Klein: Is climate science serious?</p>
    <p>11.00 Benoît Rittaud: Epistemology of Climate Change</p>
    <p>11.20 Piers Corbyn: The total failure of the ManMade Climate Change story</p>
    <p>11.40 Discussion</p>
    <p>12:00–13.00 Lunch (at your own)</p>
    <p>13.00 Thomas Wysmuller: Sea-level rise and CO2</p>
    <p>13.20 Maria Araujo: Sea level data in the Iberian Peninsula</p>
    <p>13.40 Nils-Axel Mörner: Modelled vs observed sea-level changes</p>
    <p>14.00 Discussion</p>
    <p>Session 6: Implications of the catastrophist anthropogenic global warming hypothesis</p>
    <p>14.10 Madhav Khandekar: Climate change and extreme weather: projection, perception and reality *</p>
    <p>14.30 Philip Foster: Climate policy, geoethics and the developing nations</p>
    <p>14.50 Christopher Monckton of Brenchley: Genocidal climate science *</p>
    <p>15.10 Discussion</p>
    <p>15.30 Tea and coffee</p>
    <p>15.50 Discussion, conclusions and communiqué</p>
    <p>17:00 Close</p>
    <p>* Keynote presentations</p>
    <head rend="h1">Donations</head>
    <p>We have no founding or extra support. Still, we need support for room-rental, coffee/tea breaks twice a day and other running expenses.</p>
    <p>We therefore call for voluntary donations.</p>
    <p>The Secretary General (morner@pog.nu] has an account prepared for this. PayPal to his e-mail works well. Directly at the conference is another easy option (but, please, tell me of your intentions so that I know how to manage our budget).</p>
    <p>Alle Informationen auch hier https://geoethic.com/london-conference-2016/</p>
  </main>
  <comments>
    <head>Neueste Kommentare</head>
  </comments>
</doc>